

Student about to graduate with an Animation and Digital Arts degree. The past couple of years I've specialized on 3D and videogames. Last year I had the chance to take a n intensive on VFX and Digital Composition in Barcelona. I am currently working on my habilities and I look forward to keep expanding my areas of knowledge.

ELIANE AXELLE HERNANDEZ

22 Y/O

+52 81 2489 1865



axelle_1100@outlook.com



axelle-hernandez



Monterrey, MX



Axelle Ho
Axelle



MAYA • BLENDER • NUKE HOUDINI • ADOBE • ARNOLD VRAY • UNITY • UNREAL ENGINE SUBSTANCE DESIGNER • PAINTER ZBRUSH • HTML • CSS • C# • VEX

- · Character Modeling
- Retopology
- Rigging
- FrontEnd
- Lighting
- VFX
- Particle Systems
- · Look Development
- · High and Lowpoly Modelling
- 3D Animation
- · Texture Design
- Shader Development
- Render
- Web Design
- · Coding for videogames
- Español Nativo
- Inglés IELTS, TOEFL 663
- Francés B1
- Alemán ÖSD A2
- Coreano A1

EDUCATION

2018 - PRESENT

Animation and Digital Art Degree

Tecnológico de Monterrey

2022 - 2023

VFX y Digital Compisition

Salle La Ramón Llull. Campus Barcelona

2023

FrontEnd -**Tecnolochicas Pro**

BecaTecnolochicas -Santander. Fundación Televisa y Microsoft

WORK EXPERIENCE

IULY 2022 - AUGUST 2022

Internship Artista 3D - Critical Hit

- High and Low poly modelling for videogames and VR
- Design and Application of PBR textures
- · Environment lighting

MARCH 2021 - JULY 2022

3D Generalist and Technical Artist - FUSE / People & **Technology**

- · Hardsurface and environmental modelling
- Lowpoly modelling and animation for videogames
- Environmental lighting for games
- Asset integration to Unreal Engine and Unity

AUGUST 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

FrontEnd Web Developer - CVA Tecnológico de Monterrey

- Web page coding por online courses for the Centro Virtual de Aprendizaje
- UI design
- Video and Image Editing

JANUARY 2020 - DECEMBER 2020

Social Responsibility - Animation and Digital Art Student Society SALAD

- General Direction of Enseñarte social service
- Coordination of students, benefactors and school authorities.
- · Creation of content and course design.

FEBRUARY 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021

Adiovisual Content Intern - Tecnológico de Monterrey

- · Content creator, Image and Video editing.
- Document translation
- · Interviewing and engaging with local and foreign teachers and collaborators.